Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES A. CORRESPONDENCE: 1855-1973
  - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 9. 1935, Mar. 26.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.J.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1935, Mar. 28.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz County Title Co. (I.G.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1935, Mar. 29.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to U.S. Dept. of Agric., T.L.
    - 12. 1935, Mar. 29.Same as # 11.
    - 13. 1935, April 3.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley National Farm Loan Assoc. (W.S.B.) to Steele., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1935, April 3.Stanford Univ., Stanford, Ca. Theodore J. Hoover to Colonel Roger Fitch re: proposal regarding water from Waddell Creek., T.L.
    - 15. 1935, April 4.S.F., Ca. Renesselar [R.E.S.] to Catherine [C.B.S.]., T.L.
    - 16. 1935, April 4.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (W.F.M.) to Santa Cruz County Title Co. re: policy of title insurance., T.L.
    - 17. 1935, April 6.Monterey, Ca. Roger S. Fitch to Will [W.F.S.] re: Waddell water use., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1935, April 19.N.P. Theodore J. Hoover to Division of Water Resources re: water matters., T.L.
    - 19. 1935, April 29.Stanford Univ., Stanford, Ca. Theodore J. Hoover to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1935, May 4.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.A.F.) to W.F.S. re: insurance., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1935, May 6.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Federal Land Bank., T.L.
    - 22. 1935, May 21.N.P. W.F.S. to Dr. Gans., T.L.
    - 23. 1935, June 4.Redwood City. Mary L. _____ (?) to W.F.S. re: water analysis., P.C.S.
    - 24. 1935, June 7.Los Angeles, Ca. Hall, Haas, & Vessey Ltd. (E.E.V.) to W.S.S. [W.F.S.] re: pea market., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1935, June 8.Santa Cruz, Ca. County 1st Nat'l. Bank (R.J.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1935, June 17.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to Will [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1935, June 18.Los Angeles, Ca. Star Produce Co. (K.H.) to W.F.S. re: pea market., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1935, June 22.N.P. W.F.S. to Fed. Land Bank., T.L.
    - 29. 1935, June 27.N.P. W.F.S. to Fed. Land Bank., T.L.
    - 30. 1935, June 28.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.E.A.) to W.F.S. re: interest credit - Farm Credit Act of 1935., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1935, July 2.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.E.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1935, Aug. 7.Lewiston, Mont. Edgar G. Worden to Catherine [C.B.S.] re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1935, Aug. 17.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1935, Sept. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (R.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1935, Sept. 16.S.F., Ca. Division of Immigration & Housing (M.E.E.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1935, Oct. 2.S.F., Ca. Equitable Life Insurance Co. of Iowa to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1935, Oct. 2.S.F., Ca. Division of Fish & Game (E.L.M.) to To Whom It May Concern re: permission granted to W.E. Fehliman to bring deer taken in Oregon into Calif., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1935, Oct. 2.S.F., Ca. Division of Fish & Game (E.L.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1935, Oct. 2.S.F., Ca. Division of Fish & Game (E.L.M.) to To Whom It May Concern re: permission granted to W.F.S. to bring into Calif. deer taken in Oregon., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1935, Oct. 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz County Title Co. (H.S.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1935, Nov. 10.S.F., Ca. State Compensation Insurance Fund (C.B.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1935, Dec. 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1. 1936, Jan. 8.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1936, Jan. 13.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. [C.B.S.] to Atkins., T.L.
    - 3. 1936, Jan. 16.S.F., Ca. Atkins, Kroll & Co. (D.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1936, Mar. 9.Betteravia, Ca. Joe Thakar to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 5. 1936, Mar. 11.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Thakar. signature barely legible., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1936, Mar. 11.Prince George Board of Trade (J.O.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1936, Mar. 15.Kleena Kleene, B.C., Canada. James Mackill to W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1936, Mar. 20.Berkeley, Ca. Co-operative Extension Work in Agric. & Home Economics (B.H.C.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1936, Mar. 21.Redwood City, Ca. Max J. Leonard, Agricultural Commissioner to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1936, Mar. 18.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Union Ice. Co., T.L.
    - 11. 1936, Mar. 21.S.F., Ca. Union Ice Co. (R.W.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1936, Mar. 28.S.F., Ca. Hallawell Seed Co. to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.
    - 13. 1936, Mar. 30.S.F., Ca. S.F. Sulphur Co. (P.M.P.) to W.F.S. Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1936, April 6.S.F., Ca. Jacobs, Malcolm & Burtt (W.U.F.) to Steele Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1936, April 14.N.P. Theo. J. Hoover to Flora E. Steele re: water pumping., T.L.
    - 16. 1936, April 17.Oakland, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley, (C.A.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1936, May 11.S.F., Ca. Jacobs, Malcolm & Burtt (W.U.F.) to W.J.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1936, May 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1936, May 18.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1936, May 26.S.C. [Santa Cruz], Ca. Worden Steele to Mother., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1936, June 1.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (J.L.) to W.F.S. re: compensation insurance., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1936, June 3.S.F., Ca. A. Levy & J. Lenter Co. (S.T.L.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1936, June 5.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (E.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1936, June 8.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. [W.F.S.] to Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell., T.L.
    - 25. 1936, June 20.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (J.L.) to W.F.S. re: workman's compensation insurance., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1936, July 22.Santa Cruz, Ca. C.E. Canfield & Son (L.C.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1936, Aug. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. C.E. Canfield & Son. (L.C.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1936, Aug. 14.S.F., Ca. Treadwell, Laughlin & Treadwell (J.L.) to W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1936, Sept. 25.S.F., Ca. Jacobs, Malcolm & Burtt (W.U.F.) to Mr. & Mrs. W.J.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1936, Sept. 26.San Jose, Ca. Pacific Gas & Electric Co. (I.B.A.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1936, Nov. 17.N.P. Mrs. W.F.S. to San Francisco Chronicle., T.L.
  - Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1. 1937, Mar. 26.Watsonville, Ca. Cornell Tractor Co. (L.F.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1937, April 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Costella Brothers (A.E.C.*) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1937, April 17.Watsonville, Ca. Santa Clara Valley Concrete Pipe Co. (J.K. per M.P.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1937, June 23.L.A., Ca. H. & F. Co. Hori to W.F.S. re: pea shipment., tel.
    - 5. 1937, June 23.N.P. W.F.S. to Neptune Meter Co., T.L.
    - 6. 1937, June 24.San Mateo, Ca. Elizabeth Kent to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 7. 1937, June 26.Los Angeles, Ca. Haal, Haas & Vessey to W.F.S. re: pea shipment., tel.
    - 8. 1937, June 26.Los Angeles, Ca. H. & F. Co. to W.F.S. re: pea shipment., tel.
    - 9. 1937, June 26.Wisteria, B.C., Canada. James E. Morgan to Steele [W.F.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 10. 1937, June 29.N.P. Farmers Cooperative Exchange (J.H.H.) to Dear Member. re: feed prices., T.L.
    - 11. 1937, July 10.S.F., Ca. Calif. Barrel Co., Ltd. (O.A.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1937, July 22.S.F., Ca. Calif. State Automobile Assoc. (C.H.A.D.) to White., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1937, July 26.Wisteria, B.C., Canada. James E. Morgan to Steele [W.F.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1937, Aug. 17.Van Couver, B.C., Canada. Game Commission (F.R.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1937, Oct. 17.S.F., Ca. Mary De Fremery Atkins to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1937, Oct. 24.S.F., Ca. Ralph to will & Cat [W.F.S. & C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1937, Oct. 30.N.P. C.B.S. to Edward Treadwell., T.L.
    - 18. 1937, Nov. 13.N.P. Unknown to Edward Treadwell., T.L.
    - 19. 1937, Dec. 15.Victoria, B.C., Canada. Dept. of Lands (F.O.M.) to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1938, Jan. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Worden [Steele] to Mother [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1938, Feb. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. County 1st Nat'l. Bank (B.L.S.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1938, Feb. 16.Salinas, Ca. Cornell Tractor Co. (F.C. Jr.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1938, Feb. 28.N.P. Farmers Cooperative Exchange (J.H.H.) to Dear Member., T.L.
    - 24. 1938, Mar. 8.Houston, Texas. Mother to Dear Child., A.L.S.
    - 25. 1938, April 1.Green Oaks, Pescadero, Ca. Unknown to Edward Treadwell., T.L.
    - 26. 1938, April 30.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Unknown to Edward Treadwell., T.L.
    - 27. 1938, May 31.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to John E. Manders., T.L.
    - 28. 1938, June 1.N.P. Farmers Cooperative Exchange (J.H.H.) to Dear Member., T.L.
    - 29. 1938, June 8.N.P. W.F.S. to Neptune Meter Co., T.L.
    - 30. 1938, June 24.S.F., Ca. Half Moon Bay Drum & Box Co. (R.C.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1938, June 28.S.F., Ca. Standard Plating Works, Inc. (H.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1938, June 29.Philadelphia, Pa. Curtis Publishing Co. to W.F.S., P.C.
    - 33. 1938, Aug. 22.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1938, Sept. 8.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1938, Sept. 11.San Leandro, Ca. A. Levy & J. Zentner Co. ([J.A.A.]) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1938, Dec. 2.Redwood City, Ca. D.P. Flynn, County Assessor to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1939, Jan. 7.Washington, D.C. Nat'l. Society, Daughters of the American Revolution (M.B.H.) to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1939, Feb. 1.Washington, D.C. War Dept. (G.G.P.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1939, Mar. 8.Santa Cruz, Ca. Calif. State Auto. Assc. (C.E.W.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1939, Mar. 12.Redwood City, Ca. H. [Righetti] to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1939, May 1.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Pacific Pipe Co., T.L.
    - 42. 1939, May 15.S.F., Ca. Elm & Wight ([F.]) to Catherine [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1939, May 27.Pescadero, Ca. Shoreland Properties, Inc. (J.A.K.) to Manual Baptist & W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1939, June 13.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Mrs. & Mr. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1939, Aug. 24.Santa Cruz, Ca. County 1st Nat'l. Bank (G.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1939, Aug. 24.Same as # 45.
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1. 1940, Jan. 25.Chicago, Ill. Grace [Storm] to C.[B.S.] re: genealogy., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1940, Jan. 26.S.F., Ca. Paul E. Springer to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1940, Feb. 3.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to W.F. Holbrook., T.L.
    - 4. 1940, Feb. 17.Los Angeles, Ca. Garner for President Committee (Z.L.C.) to Democrats of Calif., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1940, Feb. 29.Redwood City., Ca. Ross & Ross to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1940, Mar. 3.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Lee Ross., T.L.
    - 7. 1940, Mar. 7.Redwood City, Ca. Ross & Ross (L.T.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1940, Mar. 11.N.P. L.C. Rausch to D. Ramaciotti., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1940, Mar. 25.Betteravia, Ca. Union Sugar Co. (H.E.P.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1940, April 10.Washington, D.C. Farm Credit Administration (A.G.B.) to Stockholders of Nat'l. Farm Loan Assc., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1940, April 20.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Ferry Morse Seed Co., T.L.
    - 12. 1940, June 10.Houston, Texas. R.A. Selle to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1940, June 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.S.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1940, July 25.Betteravia, Ca. Union Sugar Co. to W.F.S., P.C.
    - 15. 1940, Aug. 1.Davenport, Ca. Davenport Artichoke Growers and Shippers to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1940, Aug. 21.Pescadero, Ca. _____(?) to Mr. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1940, Aug. 30.Pescadero, Ca. Lagune Farm Co. to Mr. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1940, Aug. 31.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] to Dr. Gans., T.L.
    - 19. 1940, Sept. 4.Redwood, City, Ca. Dept. of Public Health & Welfare (C.C.G.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1940, Sept. 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. Bank of America (W.C.*) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1940, Sept. 14.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Mecchi., T.L.
    - 22. 1940, Oct. 4.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Cooperative Exchange, Inc. (G.A.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1940, Oct. 6.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] to Farmers Cooperative Exchange, T.L.
    - 24. 1940, Oct. 11.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (D.H.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1940, Oct. 22.San Jose, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric., Agric. Conservation Committee (H.L.H.) to Sugar - Beet Grower., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1940, Oct. 23.N.P. Soquel Wharehouse Co. to W.F.S., P.C.
    - 27. 1940, Oct. 24.S.F., Ca. J. Mecchi & Co. (L.F.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1940, Oct. 26.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.B.S. to J. Mecchi Co., T.L.
    - 29. 1940, Nov. 5.San Mateo, Ca. Republican Headquarters (W.T.C.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1940, Nov. 5.San Jose, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric. Agric. Conservation Assc. (H.L.H.) to Sugar Beet Grower re: Sugar Beet Act of 1937., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1940, Nov. 14.Betteravia, Ca. Union Sugar Co. (H.A.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1940, Nov 18.San Jose, Ca. U. S. Department of Agric. Agric. Conservation Assc. (H.L.H.) to Farmers & Ranchmen in San Mateo County., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1940, Nov. 20.San Jose, Ca. San Mateo County Agricultural Conservation Committee (H.L.H.) to Unknown re: 1941 farm allotment & productivity index., T.L.S.
    - 34. Same as # 33.
    - 35. Same as # 33.
    - 36. 1940, Nov. 27.San Jose, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, San Mateo County Agric. Conservation Assc. (H.L.H.) to Unknown., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1940, Dec. 2.Betteravia, Ca. Union Sugar Co. (H.A.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1940, Dec. 18.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1940, Dec. 30.S.F., Ca. Heltman & Scampini (W.E.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1. 1941, Jan. 1.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Kellogg Seed Co., T.L.
    - 2. 1941, Jan. 2.Pescadero, Ca. Lagune Farm Co. to Mr. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1941, Jan. 14.Pescadero, Ca. Bank of America (G.C.G.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1941, Jan. 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.S.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1941, Jan. 28.Washington, D.C. Congressman John Z. Anderson to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1941, Jan. 30.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.[B.]S. to Unknown re: irrigation pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1941, Jan. 30.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. C.B.S. to Briscoe Kibbey re: irrigation pipe line., T.L.
    - 8. 1941, Feb. 3.N.P. Senator H.R. Judah to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1941, Feb. 7.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1941, Feb. 7.Sacramento, Ca. Dept. of Public Works (B.K.) to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.] re: irrigation pipe line., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1941, Feb. 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1941, Feb. 22.Pescadero. _____(?) to Mr. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 13. 1941, Feb. 27.Redwood City, Ca. Dept. of Agric. San Mateo County (M.J.L.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1941, Mar. 8.Salinas, Ca. Kellogg Seed Co. (E.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1941, Mar. 10.Alvarado, Ca. Mr. & Mrs. Lawrence Apodaca to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.
    - 16. 1941, Mar. 20.S.F., Ca. Ferry-Morse Seed Co. (J.J.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1941, Mar. 24.Sacramento, Ca. F. Lagomarsino & Sons (A.J.L.) to W.F.S. re: pea crops., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1941, April 3.Salinas, Ca. Southern Pacific Milling Co. ([R.]W.A.) to W[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1941, April 16.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. C.B.S. to Governor of Calif. re: irrigation pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1941, April 16.Same as # 19.
    - 21. 1941, April 16.Salinas, Ca. Kellogg Seed Co. (E.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1941, April 17.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to George F. Hellesoe., T.L.
    - 23. 1941, April 18.N.P. Kellogg Seed Co. of Calif. to Calif. State Laboratory., T.L.
    - 24. 1941, April 20.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Germain Seed Co., T.L.
    - 25. 1941, May 10.San Jose, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric., San Mateo County Agric. Conservation Assc. (H.L.H.) to Sugar Beet Grower. re: 1941 Sugar Beet Program., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1941, May 16.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1941, June 9.Santa Cruz, Ca. County 1st Nat'l. Bank of Santa Cruz to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1941, July 2.S.F., Ca. Eckert-Etienne Engineering Corp. (E.J.E.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1941, July 9.U.S. Dept. of Agric., San Mateo County Agric. Conservation Assc. (H.L.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1941, July 12.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (D.H.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1941, July 15.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (D.H.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1941, July 23.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Smith, Emery & Co., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1941, July 24.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.[B.]S. to Treadwell & Laughlin., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1941, July 25.S.F., Ca. Smith, Emery & Co. to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1941, July 28.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1941, Aug. 4.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (D.H.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1941, Aug. 4.N.P. Dorothy Huggins to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1941, Aug. 9.S.F., Ca. Calif. Hist. Society (D.H.H.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1941, Aug. 16.Santa Cruz, Ca. A.E. Allegrini, M.D. & Mike Morelli to George Miller re: crop damage permits., T.L.
    - 40. 1941, Sept. 5.Oakland, Ca. Clyde D. Bird to W.F.S. re: liability insurance rate for pipeline., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1941, Sept. 29.Redwood City, Ca. Pacific Gas & Electric Co. (L.G.O.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1941, Oct. 8.Fort Ord, Ca. Col. Roger S. Fitch to Worden Steele., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1941, Oct. 20.Redwood City, Ca. Pansy Jewett Abbott, County Superintendent of Schools to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1941, Oct. 21.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1941, Oct. 22.S.F., Ca. Division of Fish & Game, Bureau of Marine Fisheries (S.H.D.) to C.B.S. re: history of whaling station in Pigeon Pt., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1941, Oct. 22.Santa Cruz, Ca. Fed. Works Agency (R.G.S.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 47. 1941, Oct. 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Robert E. Burton to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 48. 1941, Oct. 28.S.F., Ca. Division of Fish & Game, Bureau of Marine Fisheries (S.H.D.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 49. 1941, Oct. 29.S.F., Ca. Fireman's Fund Indemnity Co. to Our Assureds., T.L.S.
    - 50. 1941, Oct. 29.S.F., Ca. Prudential Insur. Co. of America (P.W. Jr.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1941, Nov. 3.Santa Cruz. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 52. 1941, Nov. 5.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (O.H.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 53. 1941, Nov. 7.S.F., Ca. The Travelers Insurance & Indemnity Co. (C.D.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1941, Nov. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1941, Nov. 14.Half Moon Bay. Pacific Gas & Electric Co. (F. R.F.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1941, Nov. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 57. 1941, Nov. 24.Fresno, Ca. Diocese of Monterey-Fresno, Chancery Office to J.J. Newbegin re: Año Nuevo Point., T.L.S.
    - 58. 1941, Nov. 24.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (S.K.A.) to Unknown re: special meeting., T.L.
    - 59. 1941, Nov. 27.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 60. 1941, Dec. 8.Sacramento, Ca. Dept. of Agric., Bureau of Livestock Identification ([E.C.H.]) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 61. 1941, Dec. 11.S.F., Ca. Prudential Insur. Co. of America (P.W. Jr.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 62. 1941, Dec. 12.S.F., Ca. Federal Works Agency (T.Z.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 63. 1941, Dec. 15.Alvarado, Ca. Laurence Apodoca to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 64. 1941, Dec. 29.San Jose, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric., San Mateo County Agricultural Conservation Assc. (H.L.H.) to Sugar Beet Grower., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1. 1942, Jan. 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Pfyffer Bros. (M.B.R.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] re: brocooli., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1942, Jan. 9.Salinas, Ca. Kellogg Seed Co. (E.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1942, Feb. 19.S.F., Ca. Marine Exchange (F.T.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1942, Feb. 24.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (O.H.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1942, Mar. 2.N.P. Farmers Cooperative Exchange, Inc. (J.H.H.) to member., T.L.S.
      (letter badly wrinkled).
    - 6. 1942, Mar. 5.Oakland, Ca. Santa Cruz Fruit Packing Co. (L.A.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1942, April 10.Hollister, Ca. Selective Service System (H.M.S.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1942, April 14.S.F., Ca. Mary De Fremery Atkins & David Atkins to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1942, April 19.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Unknown [C.B.S.] to Local Board No. 122 re: claim for deferment of Diascoro Tibulan Tocong, Green Oak Ranch worker, and the general labor situation., T.L.
    - 10. 1942, April 24.Ootsa (?) Lake, B.C. Jim to Will [W.F.S.] re: effect of W.W. II on livestock prices., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1942, April 29.San Jose, Ca. Pacific Gas & Electric Co. (L.G.O.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1942, May 6.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Unknown [C.B.S.] to George W. Webb., T.L.
    - 13. 1942, May 28.S.F., Ca. Twelfth Naval District (C.H.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1942, May 29.S.F., Ca. Yuenking & Co. ([M.G.W.]) to W.F.S. re: sugar peas., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1942, June 2.S.F., Ca. Calif. State Auto. Assc. Inter-Insur. Bureau to County 1st. Nat'l. Bank., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1942, June 8.[Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca.]. [W.F.S.] to State Director of Selective Service., tel.
    - 17. 1942, June 12.San Jose, Ca. Mechanical Farm-Equipment Distributors (N.G.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1942, June 16.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Benetti & Silva (M.T.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1942, June 17.N.P. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (R.H.H.) to Unknown., T.L.
    - 20. 1942, June 26.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (H.C.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1942, July 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. London Guarantee & Accident Co., Ltd. (J.J.J.) to Fed. Land Bank., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1942, July 29.San Jose, Ca. Anglo-Calif. Nat'l. Bank (W.H.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.
    - 23. Same as # 22.
    - 24. 1942, Aug. 8.San Jose, Ca. Mechanical Farm-equipment Distribution (H.S.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1942, Aug. 19.S.F., Ca. Coastal Information Branch Office (C.J.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1942, Aug. 31.Betteravia, Ca. Union Sugar Co. (R.T.) to Beet Growers., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1942, Sept. 1.Des Moines, Iowa. Equitable Life Insur. Co. (D.C.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1942, Sept. 4.Des Moines, Iowa. Equitable Life Insur. Co. (D.C.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1942, Sept. 15.N.P. Office of Price Administration (F.C.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1942, Sept. 15.S.F., Ca. Office of Price Administration (F.C.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1942, Oct. 22.N.P. L. to Kate [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 32. 1942, Nov. 4.S.F., Ca. 12th Naval District. (C.J.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1942, Nov. 7.Swanton. [H.]H. Purdy to Will [W.F.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1942, Dec. 22.Topaz, Utah. [Mutan & Suiki Muneno] to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 35. 1942, Dec. 29.S.F., Ca. Fireman's Fund Indemnity Co. (R.J.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.